I hope you enjoyed this course
我希望你们能够喜欢上这门课程
【翻译：史红光 校对/审核：AcceptedDoge】
and to help you complete it
为了帮助你们完成这门课程
I want to make sure that
我想要确保
there are a few course resources that you know about
你们知道一些课程资源
first if you have any questions
首先如果你们有任何疑问
or you want to discuss anything with the classmates
或者想和这个课程内其它同学讨论任何问题
or the teaching staff including me
或者想和包括我在内的教学人员讨论任何问题
or if you want to file a bug report
或者是想要归档一个错误报告
the best place to do that is the discussion forum
论坛是去做这些事情最好的地方
the teaching staff and I
我和其他教学人员
will be monitoring that regularly
将定期关注论坛里的这些东西
and this is also a good place for you to get answers to your questions from your classmates
并且这也是一个从与你一同学习本课程的同学那获取答案的好地方
or if you wish try to answer your classmates' questions
如果你想要回答你的同学们的问题
to get to the discussion forum from this course home page
可以从课程首页来到课程的论坛
if you look at this menu bar on the left you also
如果你看到左侧的这个菜单栏
might look a bit different than mine
可能会看起来和我的有些不一样
but they'll do this discussion forum tab
但是他们将会做这个论坛标签
which gives you click on
当你点击它的时候
gives you to the discussion forum
将会打开课程的论坛
the best way to ask questions is on the discussion forum
在论坛上提问是问问题的最好方法
but it for some reason you need to contact us directly
但是出于某些原因你可能需要直接联系我们
or let us know about some problem
或者是想让我们知道一些问题
feel free also to email us at this email address
尽管把邮件发送到这个邮箱地址
I promise we will read every email
我保证我们会阅读每一个邮件
and we'll try to
并且尽力去
address commonly occurring issues
解决普遍出现的问题
although depending on the email volume
同样由于电子邮件的数量很多
I can't guarantee that we'll be able to
我不保证我们能够
reply promptly to every email
迅速回复每一个邮件
but we will read every email that you send
但是我们会阅读你们发送的每一封邮件
next I know that there are other companies
另外我知道有些其它公司
that wish to train maybe large numbers of employees with deep learning
想要给大批的职员培训深度学习
if you're responsible for employee training in your company
如果你们对在你们公司进行培训的职员负有责任
and would like to train a hundred or more employees
并且会培训上百或者更多的雇员
with deep learning expertise
让深度学习专家来培训
please feel free to get in touch at this email and
尽管用这个电子邮箱与我们联系
we'll see if we can help you
我们将看看是否能够帮助你们
we're just in the early phases of developing the university academic program
我们处在开发大学学术课程的早期阶段
but if you're a university
instructor or a university administrator
如果你是大学里的领导或者管理人员
interested in offering a deep learning course at your university
并且对在你们学校提供一门深度学习课程感兴趣
please feel free to contact us at this email address
请尽管通过这个邮箱地址联系我们
though I hope that gives you more resources to complete the course
我会给你们提供更多的资源来完成这门课程
maybe I'll see some of you in the discussion forums
我将在论坛中参与你们的讨论
and best of luck
祝你们好运